[{"answer": "I think it's a great comeback.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "That is so typical of Nike, Piers.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Is that an advised position for Nike, do you think, to say that look, in the end, winning is all that counts, it supersedes everything, even the kind of marital disharmony that he went through?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, that's possible.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Do you think that a more relaxed, happy Tiger has been the answer to a lot of his problems?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there is already a film made called \"The Framing of Joe Paterno Part One.\"", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "What is the purpose of the film that you are making?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Do you think Jerry Sandusky is a pedophile?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Well, actually -- wait a minute.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "So why would you want to give him the oxygen of being able to talk about his victim?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I'm not actually sure.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "You don't remember slapping towels yourself, do you?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I am sure.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "You're sure you never saw Mike McQueary?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Here's how.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "How does that have anything to do with Joe Paterno?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what, let's take a break.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Did you not say that?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "See if you can calm down.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Did you not say that?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Jerry Sandusky as I said in the previous segment had his day in court.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "You don't dispute that Jerry Sandusky abused boys in the shower and this boy in particular in the shower, right?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "He was allegedly fired for not protecting the very boy whose interview I'm holding in my hand, the day he got fired that there was nothing -- no reason to protect him.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Do you know why Joe Paterno was fired?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "An employee claimed Sandusky abused a young boy in the shower.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "You are going to quote the Penn State Board of Trustees?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Because he reported it to the board.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Zero.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "How much money you making from it?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "This is --", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "You don't make any money?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "No, absolutely.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Did you make any money from NBC?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Not a single penny.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "You didn't make a single penny?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "I'm trying to figure out what the truth of the matter is.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "Your motivation seems to be to clear Joe Paterno, right?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "I want to find out the truth.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Please stop being such an idiot, OK?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I'm trying to find the truth.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "On behalf of the man you say you are trying to clear his name, right?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "You are now attacking his family?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "That's exactly my motivation.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "Why are you so keen to make these victims go through more pain?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "He didn't know that was happening.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "If he had done any more to stop Sandusky over years of abusing boys?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I believe that Jerry Sandusky and the victim say almost exactly the same thing occurred.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "What do you think did occur then?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Let me bring in somebody else who knows all about this, CNN correspondent Sara Ganim who won a 2012 Pulitzer Prize for our coverage this story.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Can you explain why he testified the way he did or allowed Mike McQueary to testify?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "You know, piers, here's the deal.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What is your take on what my guest has been saying?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "You know, it's a shame that our children grow up around children like this, and that children can actually grow up and do things like this.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What does it say about this country that two young boys could even consider perpetrating such a crime?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I have no doubts that the shooter they have in custody -- I've seen his photo on another reporter's cell phone of the man that they have in custody.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Do you have any doubt that the two that have been charged are the ones that committed this crime?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Alive, walking around, waking me up.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "How would you like to remember his short life?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I think it's a loss of values.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "When you hear that two young American boys have been charged with murder, one of whom is alleged to have gone up and shot that woman's baby in the head in a stroller, what is going wrong that can allow that mentality?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I think the attitude towards gay rights has changed so dramatically.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "And the way that this is moving in America so fast now in favor of gay rights and gay people getting the same rights as everybody else, would you have gone through the same kind of abyss?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I try, Piers, at this point in my life not to be in serious judgment of any person except myself, and to try to do good as I see it ought to be done.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Do you look at him and think redemption, I've been there, know what it's like?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "They also deserve punishment.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Do they deserve redemption?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "I've been watching most of your show tonight, Piers.", "docId": "130325pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Tavis, let me ask you, fascinating clip there from you show, but what do you do about these two kids in Georgia who have murdered a bay in a stroller?", "qSentId": 631}]